In this clip, I'm going to show you how to cut the throat out of the fish.
Okay?
You could leave the backbone on.
We try not to waste any of the fish.
Usually, in the fish business, you paid for the whole fish.
You've paid for everything you see here, so you don't want to throw anything away that you can resell, that someone can eat.
Once again, a natural resource.
We're going to; you want to break the backbone.
Okay, we're going to twist, grab the head and the backbone; we're going to twist the head and break the backbone and pull it off the head.
We're going to take this backbone and we're going to resell it to a seafood market.
These backbones are loaded with meat, flavor, they make great chowder, gumbo, or you can just cook it up and pick the meat off with a fork.
There's a lot of good meat on here, a lot of good flavor and we don't want to waste anything.
Chefs love these.